(Sheldon:)Satellites are down. Solar flares.
-There are no solar flares now.
SHELDON: Yes, there are.
(Raj:)Dude, I'm an astrophysicist. If there
were solar flares, I'd be all up in it.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, I misspoke.
(Sheldon:)What I meant to say
was my battery died.
(Leonard:)-What the hell was that about?
-I don't know.
(Raj:)Do you think this is really Hillary Clinton
doing it with Oprah?
Aw, we really need to get you a girl.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SHELDON:
Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Leonard.
(Sheldon:)-Leonard.
-Oh, just come in!
(Sheldon:)Thanks for seeing me
on such short notice.
(Leonard:)What do you want, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Maybe this isn't a good time.
(Leonard:)Tell me why you woke me up
or I swear to God I will kill you.
(Sheldon:)Do you really think death threats are an
appropriate way to begin conversation?